<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-us" /><updated>2022-04-23T20:30:22-07:00</updated><id>https://queerkahani.com/podcast/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Queer Kahani</title><subtitle>Queer Kahani is a quirky and curious podcast of bite-sized queer stories told in an interactive interview format - happy stories, sad stories, coming out stories, closing in stories, first loves, worst loves, epiphanies, recipes, and everything in between. Learn more at https://queerkahani.com</subtitle><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><entry><title type="html">Episode 3: The Queer Side of SEAF</title><link href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 3: The Queer Side of SEAF" /><published>2022-02-22T22:02:22-08:00</published><updated>2022-02-22T22:02:22-08:00</updated><id>https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="the-queer-side-of-seaf">The Queer Side of SEAF</h3>

<p>This week on the podcast we have the incredible Sophia Iannicelli, Executive Director of the Pan Eros Foundation and the Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF). With SEAF coming up soon (April 29), many queer friends have been asking me whether SEAF was inclusive of queer folx, and while I have emphatically told them yes myself, I wanted folx to hear it directly from the director herself. In a wonderfully wide-ranging and dynamic conversation, we talk all about SEAF, eroticism, art, and consent as well as queerness. Since this episode is on the longer side, here’s a list of topics and timestamps from the interview.</p>

<ul>
  <li>[00:53] Introduction to the Pan Eros Foundation and SEAF</li>
  <li>[03:24] Consent and the Consent Academy</li>
  <li>[07:23] “You can’t consent to art”</li>
  <li>[09:48] Making SEAF a safe space to be bravely uncomfortable in</li>
  <li>[14:10] Creating a better sense of us via a greater understanding between people</li>
  <li>[15:58] Using art to teach what joy and enjoyment can mean for others</li>
  <li>[18:02] The role of art docents at SEAF</li>
  <li>[19:55] Different types of art at SEAF: from abstract to “parts into parts”</li>
  <li>[21:33] How docents and artists interact with attendees</li>
  <li>[23:36] Artists meeting and collaborating with each other at SEAF</li>
  <li>[27:05] SEAF has been built by queer people from the very first event</li>
  <li>[31:38] Erotic art can expand your sense of what turns you on</li>
  <li>[33:45] Bringing erotic art to the masses</li>
  <li>[35:38] The impact of moving to Seattle Center</li>
  <li>[37:20] Why art about our erotic lives is important</li>
  <li>[39:38] Reactions to SEAF from the traditional art community</li>
  <li>[42:37] Bringing erotic art to more galleries</li>
  <li>[45:00] The art of directing SEAF</li>
  <li>[46:41] What SEAF is not</li>
  <li>[48:15] The SEAF experience for attendees: come with your walls down</li>
  <li>[50:06] Experiencing SEAF alone vs. with others</li>
  <li>[55:40] The literary category at SEAF</li>
  <li>[61:29] Sophia’s highlights for SEAF 2022</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sophia-iannicelli-9377b36/">Sophia Iannicelli</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.seattleerotic.org/the-festival/">Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF)</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.pan-eros.org/">Pan Eros Foundation</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.consent.academy/">The Consent Academy</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.pan-eros.org/galleryerato/">Gallery Erato (Permanent Gallery for SEAF Art)</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/rae_akino/">Artist Rae Akino (@rae_akino)</a></li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wide-ranging conversation with Sophia Iannicelli, Executive Director of the Pan Eros Foundation and the Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF), about SEAF, eroticism, art, consent, as well as queerness.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 2: Coming Out Twice</title><link href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 2: Coming Out Twice" /><published>2021-12-24T20:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-24T20:30:00-08:00</updated><id>https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="coming-out-twice">Coming Out Twice</h3>

<p>Beckon tells us the story of how she’s had to come out twice over the course of her life, in two very different societal contexts. Along the way, we talk about interactions with societal norms, how to create safer spaces, how coming out might be different in 2021 compared to the early 2000s, and some of Beckon’s favorite queer resources.</p>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mkik808/">Mark Kanemura (@mkik808)</a> - a wonderfully positive, queer presence on Instagram</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/pattiegonia/">Pattie Gonia (@pattigonia)</a> - queer environmentalist increasing queer representation in the great outdoors</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beckon tells us the story of how she's had to come out twice over the course of her life, in two very different societal contexts. Along the way, we talk about interactions with societal norms, how to create safer spaces, how coming out might be different in 2021 compared to the early 2000s, and some of Beckon's favorite queer resources.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 1: Welcome to Queer Kahani</title><link href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 1: Welcome to Queer Kahani" /><published>2021-12-05T20:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-05T20:30:00-08:00</updated><id>https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="welcome-to-queer-kahani">Welcome to Queer Kahani</h3>

<p>In this introductory episode, I discuss the origins, intentions, and format of the podcast, including the meaning of the phrase “Queer Kahani.” I also give you a bit of background about me and why I made this podcast. Finally, I explain how to submit your own stories.</p>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/submitastory.html">Submit a Story</a> - instructions on how to submit a story</li>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com">Queer Kahani</a> - the site that contains this podcast</li>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com/aboynamedsu.html">A Boy Named Su</a> - my book about my journey into genderqueerness</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this introductory episode, I discuss the origins, intentions, and format of the podcast, including the meaning of the phrase "Queer Kahani." I also give you a bit of background about me and why I made this podcast.Finally, I explain how to submit your own stories.]]></summary></entry></feed>