<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-us" /><updated>2023-05-31T21:00:08-07:00</updated><id>https://sumutasib.com/podcast/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Queer Kahani</title><subtitle>Queer Kahani is a quirky and curious podcast of bite-sized queer stories told in an interactive interview format - happy stories, sad stories, coming out stories, closing in stories, first loves, worst loves, epiphanies, recipes, and everything in between. Learn more at https://queerkahani.com</subtitle><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><entry><title type="html">Episode 4: Clitaurus Chronicles</title><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-4-clitaurus-chronicles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 4: Clitaurus Chronicles" /><published>2023-01-28T15:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-01-28T15:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-4-clitaurus-chronicles</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-4-clitaurus-chronicles.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="clitaurus-chronicles">Clitaurus Chronicles</h3>

<p>In this episode, I interview the brilliant Breona Mendoza, a queer Seattle therapist, sex therapist, sex educator, and author. We discuss her delightful book, “Clitaurus Chronicles” (llustrated by Danny Tayara) in which we follow the adventures of Clitty as she navigates a maze of characters, assumptions, and expectations in search of the sensations that are just right for her. The adorable illustrations from artist Danny Tayara bring the book to life, and the highly approachable writing style makes it a gentle guide to sexploration for a wide range of readers. Along with Clitty’s story, the book teaches us about consent and gives us guidance on how to have those difficult conversations with our partners about what feels best for our bodies. We also learn more about what sex therapy is and hear about a wonderful set of sex education resources for those wanting to learn more.</p>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.papeachupress.com/product-page/clitaurus-chronicles-by-breona-mendoza-illustrated-by-danny-tayara">“Clitaurus Chronicles” by Breona Mendoza and Danny Tayara (book)</a> - product page at Papeachu Press where you can preview the content and order a copy of the book.</li>
  <li><a href="https://colorful-therapy.com/about-me">colorful-therapy.com</a> - Breona’s website.</li>
  <li><a href="https://colorful-therapy.com/sex-ed">Breona’s sex education resources</a> - Additional Clitaurus Chronicles material and other sex education resources on Breona’s website.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/clitauruschronicles/">@clitauruschronicles</a> - Clitty’s instagram account.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.aasect.org/">AASECT</a> - American association of sexuality educators, counselors, and therapists, providing training, community and visibility to promote the understanding of human sexuality and healthy sexual behavior.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.aasect.org/referral-directory">AASECT directory of sex therapists</a> - directory of AASECT certified educators, counselors, and therapists for education, counseling, and therapy purposes.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/therapists">Psychology Today directory of therapists</a> - a list of mental health professional indexed by location and specialty.</li>
  <li><a href="https://ingersollgendercenter.org/">Ingersoll Gender Center</a> - one of the oldest organizations by and for transgender and gender nonconforming communities in the United States that provides mutual support through peer led support groups, advocacy in navigating resources, community organizing, and education.</li>
  <li><a href="https://thegalap.org">GALAP (the Gender Affirming Letter Access Project)</a> - an organization of independent clinicians committed to providing gender affirming care that writes letters of support for trans folks needing them for surgeries.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.shelterwoodcollective.com">Shelterwood</a> - a therapy group in Seattle with the mission to cultivate whole-person healing for collective well-being.</li>
  <li><a href="https://papaya-project.org/">Papaya Project</a> - sex education materials, workshops, and resources for talking to parents/kids about sex.</li>
  <li><a href="https://papaya-project.org/events/">Papaya Project Events, including Sex Trivia</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.papeachupress.com">Papeachu Press</a> - the publisher of “Clitaurus Chronicles.”</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.fruitbowlpodcast.com/podcast/s4e18breona">Fruit Bowl podcast episode with Breona</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.dannytayara.com/">Danny Tayara’s portfolio</a> - the illustrator for Clitaurus Chronicles.</li>
  <li><a href="https://threedollarbillcinema.org/reelqueeryouth">Real Queer Youth</a> - a program for teaching filmmaking to young queer folx.</li>
  <li><a href="https://camptentrees.org/">Camp Ten Trees</a> - a wonderful camp for queer and trans youth.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.behance.net/erinzingre?locale=en_US">Erin Zingre</a> - an artist behind “Lisa Stank” and creator of the “Ling” character in the book.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/22609341-come-as-you-are">“Come as You Are” by Emily Nagoski (book)</a> - an exploration of sexual pleasure for people with vulvas.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.goodreads.com/en/book/show/48765886-magnificent-sex">“Magnificent Sex” by Peggy Kleinplatz (book)</a> - an ethnographic study on optimal sexual experiences.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.humpfilmfest.com/">HUMP film festival</a> - an indie porn film festival for every body.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.seattleerotic.org/">Seattle Erotic Art Festival (SEAF)</a> - an art festival exploring and celebrating sex, sexuality, and eroticism in its myriad forms.</li>
  <li><a href="https://shrimpteeth.com">Shrimp Teeth</a> - queer, polyamorous, and kinky educational resources; see also <a href="https://www.instagram.com/shrimpteeth/">@shrimpteeth on instagram</a>.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt8226854">The Dilemma of Desire (film)</a> - a documentary discussing how the clitoris has been left out of sex education.</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.cravefoundation.org/sophia-wallace">Sophia Wallace</a> - an artist who speaks regularly about misinformation in sex education.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Breona Mendoza about her book, Clitaurus Chronicles (illustrated by Danny Tayara), and her work as a therapist, sex therapist, and sex educator.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 3: The Queer Side of SEAF</title><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 3: The Queer Side of SEAF" /><published>2022-02-22T22:02:22-08:00</published><updated>2022-02-22T22:02:22-08:00</updated><id>https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-3-the-queer-side-of-SEAF.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="the-queer-side-of-seaf">The Queer Side of SEAF</h3>

<p>This week on the podcast we have the incredible Sophia Iannicelli, Executive Director of the Pan Eros Foundation and the Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF). With SEAF coming up soon (April 29), many queer friends have been asking me whether SEAF was inclusive of queer folx, and while I have emphatically told them yes myself, I wanted folx to hear it directly from the director herself. In a wonderfully wide-ranging and dynamic conversation, we talk all about SEAF, eroticism, art, and consent as well as queerness. Since this episode is on the longer side, here’s a list of topics and timestamps from the interview.</p>

<ul>
  <li>[00:53] Introduction to the Pan Eros Foundation and SEAF</li>
  <li>[03:24] Consent and the Consent Academy</li>
  <li>[07:23] “You can’t consent to art”</li>
  <li>[09:48] Making SEAF a safe space to be bravely uncomfortable in</li>
  <li>[14:10] Creating a better sense of us via a greater understanding between people</li>
  <li>[15:58] Using art to teach what joy and enjoyment can mean for others</li>
  <li>[18:02] The role of art docents at SEAF</li>
  <li>[19:55] Different types of art at SEAF: from abstract to “parts into parts”</li>
  <li>[21:33] How docents and artists interact with attendees</li>
  <li>[23:36] Artists meeting and collaborating with each other at SEAF</li>
  <li>[27:05] SEAF has been built by queer people from the very first event</li>
  <li>[31:38] Erotic art can expand your sense of what turns you on</li>
  <li>[33:45] Bringing erotic art to the masses</li>
  <li>[35:38] The impact of moving to Seattle Center</li>
  <li>[37:20] Why art about our erotic lives is important</li>
  <li>[39:38] Reactions to SEAF from the traditional art community</li>
  <li>[42:37] Bringing erotic art to more galleries</li>
  <li>[45:00] The art of directing SEAF</li>
  <li>[46:41] What SEAF is not</li>
  <li>[48:15] The SEAF experience for attendees: come with your walls down</li>
  <li>[50:06] Experiencing SEAF alone vs. with others</li>
  <li>[55:40] The literary category at SEAF</li>
  <li>[61:29] Sophia’s highlights for SEAF 2022</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sophia-iannicelli-9377b36/">Sophia Iannicelli</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.seattleerotic.org/the-festival/">Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF)</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.pan-eros.org/">Pan Eros Foundation</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.consent.academy/">The Consent Academy</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.pan-eros.org/galleryerato/">Gallery Erato (Permanent Gallery for SEAF Art)</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/rae_akino/">Artist Rae Akino (@rae_akino)</a></li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wide-ranging conversation with Sophia Iannicelli, Executive Director of the Pan Eros Foundation and the Seattle Erotic Arts Festival (SEAF), about SEAF, eroticism, art, consent, as well as queerness.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 2: Coming Out Twice</title><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 2: Coming Out Twice" /><published>2021-12-24T20:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-24T20:30:00-08:00</updated><id>https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-2-coming-out-twice.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="coming-out-twice">Coming Out Twice</h3>

<p>Beckon tells us the story of how she’s had to come out twice over the course of her life, in two very different societal contexts. Along the way, we talk about interactions with societal norms, how to create safer spaces, how coming out might be different in 2021 compared to the early 2000s, and some of Beckon’s favorite queer resources.</p>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mkik808/">Mark Kanemura (@mkik808)</a> - a wonderfully positive, queer presence on Instagram</li>
  <li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/pattiegonia/">Pattie Gonia (@pattigonia)</a> - queer environmentalist increasing queer representation in the great outdoors</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beckon tells us the story of how she's had to come out twice over the course of her life, in two very different societal contexts. Along the way, we talk about interactions with societal norms, how to create safer spaces, how coming out might be different in 2021 compared to the early 2000s, and some of Beckon's favorite queer resources.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 1: Welcome to Queer Kahani</title><link href="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 1: Welcome to Queer Kahani" /><published>2021-12-05T20:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-05T20:30:00-08:00</updated><id>https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sumutasib.com/podcast/episodes/episode-1-welcome-to-queer-kahani.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="welcome-to-queer-kahani">Welcome to Queer Kahani</h3>

<p>In this introductory episode, I discuss the origins, intentions, and format of the podcast, including the meaning of the phrase “Queer Kahani.” I also give you a bit of background about me and why I made this podcast. Finally, I explain how to submit your own stories.</p>

<h3 id="links">Links:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com/podcast/submitastory.html">Submit a Story</a> - instructions on how to submit a story</li>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com">Queer Kahani</a> - the site that contains this podcast</li>
  <li><a href="https://queerkahani.com/aboynamedsu.html">A Boy Named Su</a> - my book about my journey into genderqueerness</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Sumu Tasib</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this introductory episode, I discuss the origins, intentions, and format of the podcast, including the meaning of the phrase "Queer Kahani." I also give you a bit of background about me and why I made this podcast.Finally, I explain how to submit your own stories.]]></summary></entry></feed>